The station has entered.
Please move to the next station.
Do you want me?
My feet are driving me crazy.
Can you give me something to fix it quickly?
My name is Naka.
Medical number is URN234567 and date of birth is 169734.
Before I prescribe you a double medication for you, is it okay for me to question you or your current condition?
Can you please describe your symptoms?
Actually I have some flaking and itchiness between the toes.
Do you have any additional symptoms like swelling or bleeding?
No.
How long have you had the symptoms?
I think after a long hard working day in the form, so I have this.
In the form?
In the form.
I am a farmer.
Have you had this, have you experienced this condition prior to your current episode?
No.
Do you have any idea on what may have caused this?
Not very sure.
Not very sure, alright.
Have you tried anything to relieve your symptoms?
No.
No, do you have any allergies?
Myobiotic to peanuts.
Peanuts, alright.
Are you currently, do you have any medical conditions that you know of?
No.
Are you currently taking any medical or counter-op prescription medications?
Are you on any supplements or vitamins?
No, all right.
If you don't mind, can I please check my resources?
Do you perhaps have a preferred formulation?
If it is a cream, it will be better.
Do you want a faster relief or like...
I think it is better to be faster.
Faster relief, alright.
I believe that you're currently experiencing tinnia, especially focus on your feet, tinnia pedis, which is most probably caused by your work.
I think you mentioned this now, but no worries, I'll provide you with a medication called the lima fine.
1% cream, you are required to apply to the affected area twice daily and please ensure your affected area is clean and dry before application.
You may use it up to 1 week, the medication up is quite strong so your symptoms may be different in 1 week.
However, this medicine may cause some slight side effects like burning, stinging and irritation, but no worries.
The side effects are tolerable and it's common.
In addition to that, I advise you to take some recommendation, which is to try to wear more breathable material shoes.
Also, make sure your feet are constantly clean and try to dry your feet with a different towel.
Do not use the same towel as your body towel.
Also, if there are family members that have these symptoms as well, you need to treat them as necessary.
Do you have any questions for me?
No questions.
All right.
If you don't mind, can you please repeat my instructions?
I understood all the information given by you.
All right.
Thank you.
I'll provide you with an addition you may refer it back at home regarding a condition of medication.
If it does not clarify your concerns and doubts, please feel free to contact the pharmacy and assist you and make possible.
However, if your symptoms persist or your condition worsens in one make time,
One big time and you may immediately seek general prediction to get your condition moderately checked by a doctor.
I hope you get by this time and thank you.
Yours please, the shirt has banded.